<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PriceOMania</string>


    <string name="search">search</string>
    <string name="and_search_ARG1">and search %1$s</string>


    <string-array name="ItemList">
        <item>India</item>
        <item>America</item>
        <item>Japan</item>
        <item>Pakistan</item>
        <item>Australiya</item>
        <item>Ruse</item>
        <item>Dubai</item>
        <item>Soudi</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="open">open</string>
    <string name="close">close</string>


    <string name="UserHint">User hint</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_card_details">CardDetails</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="productdesc">The Apple iPhone 7 Plus is the latest single SIM smartphone by Apple
                       It is available in five different color variants for example, Jet Black, Silver, Gold, Black and Rose Gold.
                       So, you can select any of them that matches your style perfectly.
      </string>
    <string name="proddesc1">As compared to Apple iPhone 6, this phone comes well equipped
        with an impressive 5.5 inch retina HD display in the resolution of 1080 by 1920 pixels
        which is the most colorful and brightest display yet. Whether you are viewing live photographs
        that you click in tropic zone or checking out the dress photos, you will get a true representation.
        Its retina HD display is integrated with 3D Touch so you can easily interact with Mail, Calendar,
        Messages, and apps in a great way. If you are watching videos, viewing images or reading an e-book,
        you will have a great visual experience. Plus, it will add life to all of your stuff, whether
        it is a photo, video or game.</string>
    <string name="proddesc2">Advanced Dual Cameras.\n
                             Brilliant 5.5 Inches Display similar to OnePlus 5.\n
                             Best-in-class Stereo Speakers.\n
                             New A10 Fusion Chip.\n
                             Durable 2900mAh Non-removable Battery.</string>

    <string name="forgpasstext">No worries! We will help you reset your password easily.
        Please let us know your email address and we will send your password.</string>

</resources>
